(sniffs)
(Leonard:)Morning.
(Penny:)Hi. Want to do
yoga with me?
(Leonard:)Um, let me just have
some coffee first,
(Leonard:)and then I'll have
the strength to tell you
(Leonard:)how much I won't be doing that.
(phone ringing)
(Leonard:)Hello?
(Sheldon:)Hello, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Hey, buddy.
Good to hear your voice.
(Sheldon:)Uh, I'm in Kingman, Arizona,
(Sheldon:)and, uh, I need you
to come pick me up.
(Leonard:)I'd love to.
(Leonard:)I'm just about
to do yoga with Penny.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I'm at
the police station.
(Sheldon:)I was robbed.
Th-They took my phone,
(Sheldon:)my wallet, my iPad, everything.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God, are you okay?
(Scene:)No,
(Sheldon:)I'm not okay.
I-I'm wearing borrowed pants,
I-I don't have I.D.,
(Sheldon:)and one of the officers here
(Sheldon:)won't stop calling me
Chicken Legs.
(Leonard:)Okay.
Uh, I'll-I'll
come get you.
(Leonard:)What's the address?
(Penny:)Hey, what's going on?
Oh.
(Leonard:)He got all of
his stuff stolen.